Guide to the Carl E. Ladd papers,1932-1943
Ladd, Carl E. papers, 1932-1943
- Carl E. Ladd papers
  - Radio Talks., 1940-43 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    Wickard, Claude R.; Wake Up, America; Broadcasting; Post-war agriculture.
  - School and Teacher Groups, Speeches., 1925-41 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    Future Farmers of America; Agricultural Adjustment Administration; Agricultural economics; Extension education; Agricultural education; Rural sociology.
  - University Groups, Speeches., 1924-37 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    Rose, Flora; Rice, James E.; New York State College of Agriculture; New York State College of Home Economics; New York State Farm Bureau Federation; New York State Agricultural Experiment Station; Extension work; Agricultural education.
  - University Groups, Speeches., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    Rose, Flora; Blanding, Sarah Gibson; New York State College of Agriculture; New York State College of Home Economics; Cornell Plantations; Bailey Hortorium; Ho-Nun-De-Kah; Farm and Home Week; Agricultural education; Faculty.
  - Articles., 1925-30 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    Roosevelt, Franklin D.; New York State Grange; Dairymen's League Cooperative Association, Inc.; Dartington Hall; Four-H Clubs; Agricultural legislation.
  - Articles., 1925-29 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    New York State Cooperative Extension Service; New York Seed Improvement Cooperative Association, Inc.
  - A Miscellaneous., 1932-33 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Agricultural Advisory Commission (Proposed National Commission)., 1933 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Morgenthau, Henry Jr.; Wallace, Henry A.; Roosevelt, Franklin D.; Myers, William I.; Federal Farm Board; Cooperatives.
  - Agricultural Conference Board., 1933 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Morgenthau, Henry Jr.; New York State Agricultural Conference Board.
  - New York State Agricultural Society., 1933 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - American Farm Bureau Federation., 1932-33 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Tugwell, Rexford G.; Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities; New York State Cooperative Extension.
  - American Agriculturist., 1932-33 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - American Country Life Association., 1932-33 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - New York State Agricultural Experiment Station., 1932-33 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Parrott, Percival J.; Hedrick, Ulysses P.; New York State Agricultural Experiment Station; Land grant institutions; Pomology.
  - New York State Agricultural Experiment Station., 1932-33 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Tukey, Harold B.
  - B Miscellaneous., 1933 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - B Miscellaneous., 1932-33 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - B Miscellaneous., 1932 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Babcock, Howard E., 1932-33 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Hoover, Herbert H.; Elmhirst, Leonard K.; Rice, James E.; Federal Farm Board; Agricultural policy.
  - Bailey, Liberty Hyde., 1932-33 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Bailey Hortorium.
  - Bernays, Edward L., 1933 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    Rogers, James R.; Wallace, Henry A.; Hoover, Herbert H.; Reconstruction Finance Corporation; Federal reserve banks; Economic trends.
  - Bliss, R. K. (Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities)., 1932-33 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Wallace, Henry A.; Pearson, Raymond A.; Bailey, Liberty Hyde; Morgenthau, Henry Jr.; Sigma Xi; American Farm Bureau Federation; Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities; Extension work; Economic policy.
  - C Miscellaneous., 1933 (Box 3, Folder 17-18)
  - C Miscellaneous., 1932-33 (Box 3, Folder 19-20)
  - Association of Civil Service Employees., 1932-33 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Cow Measuring Tape., 1930-33 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - SUNY Agricultural and Technical Institute at Cobleskill., 1932 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Cornell in China Club., 1933 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    Buck, J. Lossing.
  - D Miscellaneous., 1933 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - D Miscellaneous., 1932 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Dairymen's League Cooperative Association, Inc., 1932-33 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    Sexauer, Fred H.; Hart, Van B.; Simons, Lloyd R.; Pearson, Frank A.; Miller, Seward A.; Dairymen's League Cooperative Association, Inc.
  - Domestic Allotment Plan., 1933 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    Cooper, Thomas P.; Bliss, Ralph K.; Christensen, Chris L.; Morgenthau, Henry Jr.; Jones, Marvin; Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities; United States House of Representatives, Agricultural Committee; County agents; Agricultural legislation.
  - E Miscellaneous., 1932-33 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Eastman, Edward R., 1932-33 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    Simons, Lloyd R.; Sexauer, Fred H.; Lehman, Herbert H.; Babcock, Howard E.; Eddy, Martha H.; American Agriculturist; Federal Land Bank of Springfield; New York State Farm Bureau Federation; Dairymen's League Cooperative Association, Inc.; Ralston Purina Company; Federal land banks; New York Milkshed.
  - Emergency Committee of the New York Milkshed., 1932 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    Alien, George N.; Sexauer, Fred H.; Dairymen's League Cooperative Association, Inc.; Nestles Food Company; New York Milkshed.
  - Epsilon Sigma Phi., 1931-33 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    Van Rensselaer, Martha; Smith, Ruby G.
  - F Miscellaneous., 1932-33 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Foster, Edward S., 1932-33 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    Hart, Van B.; Wallace, Henry A.; O'Neal, Edward A.; Wagner, Robert F.; New York State Farm Bureau Federation; Federal Land Bank of Springfield; Farm Credit Administration; New York State Dept. of Agriculture and Markets; New York State College of Agriculture; United States Food and Drug Administration; Economic policy; Agricultural legislation; Agricultural credit; Dairy industry; Agricultural education.
  - Feed Dealers., 1932-33 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    Riford, Lloyd S.; Fricke, Richard F.; Abbott, Lewis; Kirkland, Leigh G.; Morrison, Frank B.; Grange League Federation; Cooperative marketing.
  - Feed Dealers., 1932 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    Mann, Albert R.; Farrand, Livingston.
  - G Miscellaneous., 1932-33 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - National Grange., 1932-33 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    Taber, Louis J.; Roosevelt, Franklin D.
  - New York State Grange., 1932-33 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    Freestone, Fred J.; Arthur, Elizabeth L.; Farm and Home Week.
  - H Miscellaneous., 1933 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - H Miscellaneous., 1932-33 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Hotels., 1932-33 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - I Miscellaneous., 1933 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - International Conference of Agricultural Economists., 1931-32 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    Elmhirst, Leonard K.; Warren, George F.; Haskell, Henry S.; Carnegie Endowment for International Peace; Dartington Hall; International Conference of Agricultural Economists; Agricultural economics.
  - International Agricultural Economic Conference., 1932-33 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    Elmhirst, Leonard K.; Warren, George F.; Sering, Max; Butler, Nicholas Murray; Haskell, Henry S.; International Conference of Agricultural Economists; Carnegie Endowment for International Peace; Dartington Hall; Agricultural economics.
  - J Miscellaneous., 1932-33 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Journal of Agricultural Research., 1932-33 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - K Miscellaneous., 1932-33 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Land Use., 1932-33 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    National Advisory and Legislative Committee on Land Use.
  - L Miscellaneous., 1932-33 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities., 1932-33 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    Cooper, Thomas P.; Martin, Oscar B.; Creel, Cecil W.; Crocheron, Bertram H.; Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities; Land grant institutions; Agricultural legislation; Depression.
  - M Miscellaneous., 1933 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - M Miscellaneous., 1932 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Miscellaneous Applications and Recommendations for Positions., 1932-33 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - SUNY Agricultural and Technical Institute at Morrisville., 1932-33 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - McKay, Andrew W., 1932-33 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    Federal Farm Board.
  - Milk, Report Joint Legislative Committee to Investigate the Milk Industry and Related Materials., 1933 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    Pitcher, Perley A.; Spencer, Leland; New York Milkshed; Dairymen's League Cooperative Association, Inc.; Sheffield Farms Company, Inc.
  - Monetary Data., 1933 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - N Miscellaneous., 1932-33 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - National Canners Association., 1932-33 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - New York Seed Improvement Cooperative Association., 1933 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    Jones, Bruce P.; Roosevelt, Franklin D.; Simons, Lloyd R.; Evans, Harold J.; New York Seed Improvement Cooperative Association, Inc.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Plant Breeding; Farm and Home Week; Seed certification.
  - New York State Gas and Electric Corporation., 1933 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - O Miscellaneous., 1932-33 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - P Miscellaneous., 1932-33 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Pearson, Raymond A., 1932-33 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Taber, Louis J.; Warburton, Clark; Mann, Albert R.; O'Neal, Edward A.; Douglas, Lewis W.; Sherley, Swagar; Butler, Tait; Roosevelt, Franklin D.; Wallace, Henry A.; Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities; American Farm Bureau Federation; Federal Farm Board; National Grange; Agricultural education.
  - R Miscellaneous., 1932-33 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Rochester Teachers' Credit Union., 1932 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Robinson, James R., 1933 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Homer, Harlan H.
  - S Miscellaneous., 1933 (Box 4, Folder 7-8)
  - S Miscellaneous., 1932 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Sheffield Producers., 1933 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Sound and Honest Money Association., 1933 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    White, Charles R.; New York State Grange; Sound and Honest Money Association; Monetary reform.
  - T Miscellaneous., 1932-33 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Miss Titus., 1932-33 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Thomas, Wilbur K., Carl Schurz Memorial Foundation., 1933 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    Warren, George F.; Thomas, Wilbur K.; Maynard, Leonard A.; Oberlaender Trust; Carl Schurz Memorial Foundation Inc.
  - Treman, Robert E., 1933 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    Osborne, Lithgow; Treman, Robert E.; Underhill, E. Victor; Lehman, Herbert H.; Gannett, Frank E.; Morgenthau, Henry Jr.; Stutz, Harry G.; Roosevelt, Franklin D.; Smith, Albert E.; New York State Dept. of Conservation; Farmers Week; Politics.
  - U Miscellaneous., 1932-33 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - V Miscellaneous., 1932-33 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - W Miscellaneous., 1932-33 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - W Miscellaneous., 1932 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - XYZ Miscellaneous., 1932-33 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - President's Office., 1933-34 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    Farrand, Livingston; Myers, William I.; Thomsen, Edward H.; Longree, Karla; Love, Harry H.; Rockefeller Foundation; Federal Land Bank of Springfield; Commonwealth Fund.
  - Provost's Office., 1933-34 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    Mann, Albert R.; Pearson, Raymond A.; Wagner, Robert F.; Schurman, Jacob G.; Lewin, Kurt; Wallace, Henry A.; Morgenthau, Henry Jr.; Homer, Harlan H.; Tugwell, Rexford G.; Roosevelt, Franklin D.; Longree, Karla; Love, Harry H.; Bailey, Liberty Hyde; United States Dept. of Agriculture; United States Forest Service; Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Entomology; Farm Credit Administration; Cornell Plantations; New Deal; Land grant institutions; Arnot Forest.
  - Buildings and Grounds., 1933-34 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Cornell University Comptroller., 1933-34 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    Bostwick, Charles D.
  - Treasurer., 1933-34 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    Rogalsky, George F.; United States Dept. of Agriculture, Extension Service; Fellowships.
  - Wheeler, Ralph H., Assistant Treasurer., 1933-34 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Business Office., 1933-34 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Agricultural Economics and Farm Management., 1933-34 (Box 4, Folder 28-29)
    Warren, George F.; Myers, William I.; Bond, Maurice C.; Catherwood, Martin P.; Hart, Van B.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Agricultural Economics; Farm Credit Administration; New York State Bankers Association; Production Credit Corporation of Springfield; United States Dept. of the Interior, Subsistence Homesteads Division; New York Milkshed; Federal funds; Milk marketing.
  - Agricultural Engineering., 1933-34 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    Robb, Bryon B.; Riley, Howard W.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Agricultural Engineering; Empire State Gas and Electric Association; Rural electrification.
  - Agronomy., 1933-34 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    Romell, Lars G.; Lyon, T. Lyttleton; Livermore, Kenneth C.; Pack, Arthur N.; Horner, Harlan H.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept of Agronomy; Soil surveys; Land classification; Federal funds.
  - Animal Husbandry., 1933-34 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    Morrison, Frank B.; Abbott, J.B.; Baldwin, Charles H.; Burrows, John T.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Animal Husbandry; Dairy Herd Improvement Association, Inc.; American Cyanamid Corporation; New York State Dairymen's Association; Animal nutrition.
  - Botany., 1933-34 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    Wiegand, Karl M.; Roe, William I.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Botany.
  - Dairy Industry., 1933-34 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    Ross, Harold E.; American Dairy Science Association.
  - Entomology., 1934 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    Needham, James G.; Alien, Arthur A.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Entomology; New York State College of Agriculture, Laboratory of Ornithology; Dutch Elm Disease; Ornithology; Comstock Hall.
  - Entomology., 1929-33 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    Needham, James G.; MacLeod, Guy F.; Gordon, Seth; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Entomology; American Game Association; New York State Agricultural Experiment Station; Comstock Hall; Wildlife conservation.
  - Agricultural Experiment Station., 1934 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    Hedrick, Ulysses P.; Horner, Harlan H.; Tressler, Donald K.; Sexauer, Fred H.; Spencer, Leland; Eastman, Edward R.; Morgenthau, Henry Jr.; Freestone, Fred J.; Tugwell, Rexford G.; Wallace, Henry A.; Breed, Robert S.; New York State Agricultural Experiment Station; Empire State Gas and Electric Association; Borden Company; Dairymen's League Cooperative Association, Inc.; New York State Grange; Dutch Elm Disease; Food processing.
  - Agricultural Experiment Station., 1933 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    Hedrick, Ulysses P.; Tressler, Donald K.; Carpenter, Dwight C.; New York State Agricultural Experiment Station.
  - Extension., 1933-34 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    Simons, Lloyd R.; New York State Cooperative Extension Service.
  - Office of the Director., 1933-34 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    Simons, Lloyd R.; Warburton, Clark; Horner, Harlan H.; Extension work.
  - Office of the Director., 1933 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    Hart, Van B.; Simons, Lloyd R.; Morgenthau, Henry Jr.; Lehman, Herbert H.; Ten Eyck, Peter G.; Roosevelt, Franklin D.; Warburton, Clark; Farm Credit Administration; New York Milkshed; National Recovery Administration; Agricultural Adjustment Administration.
  - Central Farm Bureau., 1933-34 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    Flansburgh, Earl A.; Kelsey, Lincoln D.; Extension work; Farm mortgages.
  - Home Bureau., 1933-34 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    Smith, Ruby G.
  - Junior Extension., 1933-34 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    Wright, William J.; Hoefer, Albert; Hopkins, E. N.; Robert M. Adams Memorial Scholarship.
  - Robinson, Montgomery., 1933-34 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Taylor, Charles A., 1933-34 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    Arthur, Elizabeth L.; Cornell School for Missionaries; New York State Grange; Extension work.
  - Farm Practice., 1933-34 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Floriculture and Ornamental Horticulture., 1933-34 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    White, Edward A.; Curtis, Ralph W.; Parker, Dan M.; Sherman, Sherrill; Garrett, Clara L.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Floriculture and Ornamental Horticulture; Sex Discrimination.
  - Forestry., 1933-34 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    Hosmer, Ralph S.; Wallace, Henry A.; Guise, Cedric H.; Abbe, Cleveland Jr.; Bentley, John Jr.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Forestry; Civilian Conservation Corps.
  - Library, Agriculture., 1933 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    Ellis, Willard W.
  - Plant Breeding., 1933-34 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    Emerson, Rollins A.; Wiggins, Roy G.; Hansen, Frank B.; Love, Harry H.; Myers, Clyde H.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Plant Breeding; Rockefeller Foundation; University of Nanking; General Education Board; Nanking Cooperative Crop Improvement Project; Genetics.
  - Plant Pathology., 1933-34 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    Longree, Karla; Massey, Louis M.; Chardon, Carlos E.; Barrus, Mortier F.; American Rose Society; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Plant Pathology; United States Dept. of Agriculture.
  - Pomology., 1933-34 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    Heinicke, Arthur J.; Mordoff, Richard A.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Pomology; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Meteorology; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept of Agronomy; Spray residues.
  - Poultry Husbandry., 1933-34 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    Rice, James E.; Krum, Walter G.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Poultry Husbandry; Agricultural Advertising and Research Service, Inc.; Poultry Science Association.
  - Naming Poultry Building., 1933-34 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    Rice, James E.
  - Poultry Headship, Letters Recommending Department Head., 1933-34 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    Benjamin, Earl W.; Hutt, Frederick B.; Halpin, James G.; Kent, Olney B.; Charles, Thomas B.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Poultry Husbandry.
  - Publications Office., 1933-34 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Resident Instruction., 1933-34 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Rural Education., 1933-34 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    Butterworth, Julian E.; Kruse, Paul J.; Farrand, Livingston; Elmhirst, Leonard K.; Stewart, Rolland M.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Rural Education; Dartington Hall.
  - Rural Social Organization., 1933-34 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    Sanderson, Dwight; Duthie, Mary E.; Beers, Howard; Wallace, Henry A.; Howard, Randolph L.; Mann, Albert R.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept of Rural Sociology; Federal Emergency Relief Administration; American Baptist Foreign Mission Society; Four-H Clubs; Extension Work.
  - Vegetable Crops., 1933-34 (Box 4, Folder 61)
    Thompson, Homer C.; Work, Paul E.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Vegetable Crops; Vegetable Growers Association of America; New York State Farm Bureau Federation; Farm Credit Administration; Empire State Potato Club.
  - Cornell Countryman., 1933-34 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Committee on Pasture Experiments., 1934 (Box 4, Folder 63)
    Savage, Elmer S.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Agronomy; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Animal Husbandry; Pasture research.
  - Committee to Make Recommendations on Seeding Home Economics and Agricultural Economics Grounds., 1934 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Course in Conservation or Game Management., 1933-34 (Box 4, Folder 65)
    Adams, William C.; Osborne, Lithgow; Needham, James G.; Allen, Arthur A.; McCay, Clive C.; New York State Dept. of Conservation; Wildlife conservation.
  - Home Economics., 1934 (Box 4, Folder 66)
    Rose, Flora; Baldwin, Charles H.; Lewin, Kurt; Jardine, James T.; New York State College of Home Economics; New York State Dept. of Agriculture and Markets; Farm and Home Week; Federal funds.
  - Home Economics., 1932-33 (Box 4, Folder 67)
    Lewin, Kurt; Waring, Ethel B.; Rose, Flora; New York State College of Home Economics; Martha Van Rensselaer Hall; Child development.
  - Home Economics., 1933-34 (Box 4, Folder 68)
    Rose, Flora; New York State College of Home Economics; Martha Van Rensselaer Hall.
  - Hotel., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Meek, Howard B.
  - New York State College of Veterinary Medicine., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Architecture., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Young, George Jr.; Roosevelt, Franklin D.; Peaslee, Horace W.; Keppel, Frederick; Mann, Albert R.; Carnegie Corporation of New York; Cornell University College of Architecture; Federal Emergency Administration of Public Works.
  - Arts and Sciences., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Lewin, Kurt; Cornell University College of Arts and Sciences.
  - Graduate School., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Rahn, Otto; Longree, Karla; Mann, Albert R.; Crawford, David L.; Cornell University Graduate School; National Research Council; Cornell United Religious Work; Colgate-Rochester Divinity School.
  - Graduate School of Education., 1931-34 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Law College., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Burdick, Charles K.; Thomson, Edward H.
  - Music Department., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Willard Straight Hall., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Elmhirst, Leonard K.
  - A Miscellaneous., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Agricultural Missions Foundation., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Reisner, John H.; Sanderson, Dwight; Landis, Benson Y.; Richtmyer, Floyd K.; Agricultural Missions Foundation, Inc.; Cornell United Religious Work; Cornell School for Missionaries; Missionaries.
  - American Agriculturist., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Eastman, Edward R.; Eaton, E.R.; Baldwin, Charles H.; Morgenthau, Henry Jr.; Babcock, Howard E.; Lehman, Herbert H.; Myers, William I.; Wallace, Henry A.; New York State Dept. of Conservation; Farm Credit Administration; Federal Land Bank of Springfield; New York State Bankers Association; Anti-Semitism; Agricultural marketing.
  - American Country Life Association., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Gray, Lewis C.; Nisonger, Hershel W.; Landis, Benson Y.; Butterworth, Julian E.; Hutcheson, John R.; American Country Life Association; Institute of Rural Affairs; Land use; Soil Conservation; Rural education; Vocational education.
  - B Miscellaneous., 1934 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - B Miscellaneous., 1933 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Babcock, Howard E., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    Gannett, Frank E.; Tugwell, Rexford G.; Warren, George F.; Corbett, Roger B.; Babcock, Howard E.; Pearson, Drew; Wallace, Henry A.; Roosevelt, Franklin D.; American Farm Bureau Federation; Grange League Federation; New Deal.
  - Bailey, Liberty Hyde., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - C Miscellaneous., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - D Miscellaneous., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Dairymen's League Cooperative Association, Inc., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    Sexauer, Fred H.; Warren, George F.; Young, Chester; Dairymen's League Cooperative Association, Inc.; National Cooperative Council; New York Milkshed; Dairy industry.
  - Dartington Hall, Leonard K. Elmhirst., 1932-34 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    Warren, George F.; Roosevelt, Eleanor; Roosevelt, Franklin D.; Wallace, Henry A.; Myers, William I.; Pearson, Frank A.; Elmhirst, Dorothy; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Agricultural Economics; International Conference of Agricultural Economists.
  - Danforth Foundation., 1934 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    Comstock, John H.; Danforth, William H.; Betten, Cornelius; Wilder, Burt G.; Ralston Purina Company; Martha Van Rensselaer Hall.
  - Democrat and Chronicle, Leo B. Skeffington., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    Skeffington, Leo B.; Roosevelt, Eleanor; Roosevelt, Franklin D.; Sibley, Harper; Bonner, J. Franklin; Gannett, Frank E.; United States Dept. of the Interior; New York State Horticultural Society; Farm and Home Week.
  - E Miscellaneous., 1934 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - F Miscellaneous., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - American Farm Bureau Federation., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    O'Neal, Edward A.; Gray, Chester H.; Roosevelt, Franklin D.; Wallace, Henry A.; White, Charles R.; Pearson, Raymond A.; Morgenthau, Henry Jr.; American Farm Bureau Federation; Farm Credit Administration; Federal funds; Extension work; New Deal; Land grant institutions.
  - New York State Farm Bureau Federation., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 27)